gopusa.com 2008-06-10

# GOPUSA - Privacy Notice

| 

  Text Size: S   M   L

|   
---  

Get a daily dose of political wit at GOPUSA. Check out our new cartoon line-up featuring some of the best cartoonists in the country!

Printer-Friendly Version

**GOPUSA PRIVACY NOTICE**

**1\. Overview.**

Privacy is very important to GOPUSA.com, Inc. ("GOPUSA"). As part of the normal operation of our services we collect and, in some cases, disclose information about you. This Privacy Notice describes the information we collect about you and what may happen to that information. Although this Privacy Notice may seem long, we have prepared a detailed policy because we believe you should know as much as possible about GOPUSA's practices so that you can make informed decisions. The privacy practices of this statement apply to the http://www.GOPUSA.com web site, the GOPUSA Eagle, and/or any of our other services and products offered by GOPUSA.

As described below, some of your personally identifiable information is disclosed to third parties and used by us and third parties. By accepting the User Agreement, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information. This Privacy Notice is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the GOPUSA Subscriber and Member Agreement located at [http://www.GOPUSA.com/legal/agreement.shtml](http://gopusa.com/legal/agreement.shtml)

**2\. The Information We Collect.**

The "GOPUSA Sites" shall mean all areas and any subscription or other products and services offered or available on the online service operated by GOPUSA on the World Wide Web, and expressly includes the GOPUSA Eagle e-mail magazine. The GOPUSA Sites consist of information services and content provided by GOPUSA, affiliates of GOPUSA, and third parties. 

At some GOPUSA Sites, you may be able to order products, enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services, or participate in one of our online forums or communities. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services. 

At some other GOPUSA Sites, you may be able to submit information about other people. For example, you might submit a person's name and e-mail address to send an electronic greeting card and, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you might submit the recipient's name and address. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages include: recipient's name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number. 

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows Œ98 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink).

**3\. How We Use the Information.**

We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you. In addition, we may use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when we make changes to our subscriber agreements, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter, or to contact you about your account with us. Moreover, we may use the information that you provide about others to enable us to send them information. From time to time, we also may use this information to offer our products, programs, or services to them. In addition, GOPUSA may on occasion combine information we receive online with outside records to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you.

The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, or services. We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services. 

We will disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request. Agents and contractors of GOPUSA who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for GOPUSA.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice. Inadvertent disclosures may result, for example, when third parties misrepresent their identities in asking the site for access to personally identifiable information about themselves for purposes of correcting possible factual errors in the data. 

**4\. Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors.**

Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. 

GOPUSA Sites sometimes may offer contests, sweepstakes, or promotions that are sponsored by or co-sponsored with identified third parties. By virtue of their sponsorship, these third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the contest, sweepstakes, or promotion. GOPUSA has no control over the third-party sponsors' use of this information.

**5\. Cookies.**

To enhance your experience with our sites, our web pages may use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. 

We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site), or to save your password in password-protected areas. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services.

**6\. Our Commitment to Security.**

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online. Unless needed to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, we will not give out your credit card information to any third party.

**7\. Notice.**

IF YOU DO NOT ACCEPT THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, YOU MAY NOT USE THE GOPUSA SITES. GOPUSA reserves the right to make changes to the GOPUSA Sites and this Agreement at any time without prior notice. This Agreement may not otherwise be amended except in a writing signed by GOPUSA.

|  |
